# Yuanyuan Li

#### CONTACT

http://yuanyuanli.me

+1 206 319 2929

#### **EDUCATION**

Cornell University Master's Degree Information Science 2015-2016 GPA:3.73/4.0

University of International Business and Economics

Bachelor's Degree

Electronic-Commerce

2010 - 2014

GPA: 3.86/4.0: RANK: 1/108

AWARDS: National Scholarship (top 1%), Beijing Merit Student (top 1%),

Leadership Scholarship, etc.

## PROGRAMMING SKILLS

**JavaScript j**Query

HTML5 CSS3

Sass/Scss Bootstrap 3

PHP SOL

**SWIFT** AngularJS

HTML CSS

JAVA D3.js

# SOFTWARE SKILLS

Photoshop Sketch 3

Axure PR Adobe Illustrator

Sublime/VIM Git/SVN

Visual Studio Code **Eclipse** 

Prezi Xcode

#### **ABOUT ME**

A passionate UI developer with background in software engineer and human computer interface design. Specializes in transferring a creative idea from sketch to high quality code. An ambitious problem solver with a keen interest in technology and UX.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Web Developer @ Supplyhouse.com

Aug 2016 - Present

- -Developed fully functional and responsive websites for e-commerce, using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, jQuery, Java, JavaScript and FreeMarker
- -Designed prototypes based on business requirements and then translated prototypes/ designs into clean, valid, and launch-ready pages with reusable UI components
- -Created code/design guidelines by interacting with graphic designer, marketers and SEs
- -Tested front-end code in multiple browsers to ensure cross-browser compatibility
- -Managed small websites in GoDaddy with Php, MySql and WordPress

## Front End Developer @ Yumso

May 2016 - Present

- -Maintained, developed and designed our startup platform connecting chefs and eaters
- -Executed and contributed to full-stack web development projects, with an emphasis on front end features, browser manipulation, and cross-browser compatibility
- -Collaborated with a virtual and cross-functional team (agile development methodology)

## IT Consulting Assistant (internship), @ PwC

Mar 2015 - Jun 2015

- -Analyzed finance system migration requirements by working closely with clients
- -Developed and tested IT system specifications, as well as managed project documents

Project Assistant (internship), @ SAP

May 2014 > Oct 2014

-Cooperated with global IT architects to redesign and SAP ERP systems for clients

Sales Operation and Channel Assistant (internship), @ NetApp

Sep 2013 - Jan 2014

-Supervised and analyzed orders by cooperating with Sales and Channel Managers

## **PROJECTS**

# Front End Developer

Sep 2015 - Dec 2015

Software Engineering Project, @Clients: MERID Research Group

- -Produced a web for online investigations by using jade, node.js, jQuery and JavaScript
- -Designed interactive prototypes to for clients following SE Development Methodologies
- -Conducted feasibility study and user experience study to test website's usability

## iOS Developer

Feb 2016 - May 2016

FitCat iOS App Development Project, @Clients: Cornell Feline Health Center

- -Developed a mobile app from sketch to an functional ready iOS app for cats health
- -Designed UI with Sketch 3 and developed with Swift, Xcode, and Firebase
- -Maintained active conversation with clients to ensure the site met needs

### **UI/UX** Designer

Feb 2016 - May 2016

Business Consulting Project, @Clients: GiveNext

- -Designed a mobile UI and marketing strategies for startup GiveNext to attract donors
- -Designed fully-interactive low quality/high quality prototypes and click-through which were used for presentations, mock-ups, as well as user-testing studies